<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mystery hunt exercise on ANT332 AWS re:Invent 2019</title>
    <link>/en/start/mysteryhunt.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mystery hunt exercise on ANT332 AWS re:Invent 2019</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 20:55:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/start/mysteryhunt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mystery hunt 1</title>
      <link>/en/start/mysteryhunt/hunt1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:44:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/start/mysteryhunt/hunt1.html</guid>
      <description>Your application developers have raised a ticket that you have to investigate. They are unable to reach their throughput goals despite scaling their application pods. What could be the issue?
Simulate the scenario Run the command below to simulate the scenario
 curl -O https://ant332.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ant332-lab-guide-artifacts/mystery_script_1.sh &amp;amp;&amp;amp; chmod +x mystery_script_1.sh &amp;amp;&amp;amp; ./mystery_script_1.sh Hint [Metricbeat Kubernetes] Overview ECS Kibana dashboard is a great place to start to get a quick high level overview of your Kubernetes environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mystery hunt 2</title>
      <link>/en/start/mysteryhunt/hunt2.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:44:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/start/mysteryhunt/hunt2.html</guid>
      <description>Your customers have complained that Guestbook website is throwing 404 not found errors. Investigate and identify the root cause.
Simulate the scenario Run the command below to simulate the scenario
curl -O https://ant332.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ant332-lab-guide-artifacts/mystery_script_2.sh &amp;amp;&amp;amp; chmod +x mystery_script_2.sh &amp;amp;&amp;amp; ./mystery_script_2.sh $URL3 Hint Remeber we created apache- index? It will have useful information to troubleshoot.
Mystery Solved Open Kibana, Double-click Discover tab. Then choose apache-* index pattern and search for 404 errors. You will see all the logs records that contain 404 errors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mystery hunt 3</title>
      <link>/en/start/mysteryhunt/hunt3.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:44:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/start/mysteryhunt/hunt3.html</guid>
      <description>Your development team has reported that redis performance has degraded over time. They suspect memory fragmentation may be the root cause. They&#39;ve asked for an easy way to get visibility into trend of memory fragmentation over a period of time.
Hint Remember we created the redis- index? Examine the contents of this index and build a visualization in Kibana.
Mystery Solved The redis- index contains all the key redis metrics collected by flunetbit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>