<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Use Amazon ES to visualize and monitor containerized applications on ANT332 AWS re:Invent 2019</title>
    <link>/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Use Amazon ES to visualize and monitor containerized applications on ANT332 AWS re:Invent 2019</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:42:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Kibana for Kubernetes Index</title>
      <link>/en/start/indices/k8s.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:44:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/start/indices/k8s.html</guid>
      <description>Click this deep link to open Kibana in your browser and follow the steps below - http://localhost:9200/_plugin/kibana
Click Mangement tab
Now click on Index Patterns
Click Create Index Pattern
Type kubernetes-* in the input box
Select @timestamp field from the drop down and Click Create Index Pattern
Kibana is now fully setup to start visualizing Kubernetes logs. Lets setup the rest of the index patterns so we can visualize all data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mystery hunt 1</title>
      <link>/en/start/mysteryhunt/hunt1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:44:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/start/mysteryhunt/hunt1.html</guid>
      <description>Your application developers have raised a ticket that you have to investigate. They are unable to reach their throughput goals despite scaling their application pods. What could be the issue?
Simulate the scenario Run the command below to simulate the scenario
 curl -O https://ant332.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ant332-lab-guide-artifacts/mystery_script_1.sh &amp;amp;&amp;amp; chmod +x mystery_script_1.sh &amp;amp;&amp;amp; ./mystery_script_1.sh Hint [Metricbeat Kubernetes] Overview ECS Kibana dashboard is a great place to start to get a quick high level overview of your Kubernetes environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Amazon Elasticsearch?</title>
      <link>/en/intro/first-content.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:44:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/intro/first-content.html</guid>
      <description>Amazon Elasticsearch Service is a fully managed service that makes it easy for you to deploy, secure, and operate Elasticsearch at scale with zero down time. The service offers open-source Elasticsearch APIs, managed Kibana, and integrations with Logstash and other AWS Services, enabling you to securely ingest data from any source and search, analyze, and visualize it in real time. Amazon Elasticsearch Service lets you pay only for what you use – there are no upfront costs or usage requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Kibana for redis index</title>
      <link>/en/start/indices/redis.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:44:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/start/indices/redis.html</guid>
      <description>Repeat the previous step to create an index pattern for redis- index. Click this deep link to open Kibana in your browser and follow the steps below - http://localhost:9200/_plugin/kibana
Click Management tab -&amp;gt; Click Index Patterns -&amp;gt; Click Create Index Pattern -&amp;gt; Type redis-* in input box -&amp;gt; Choose ***@timestamp*** from drop down-&amp;gt; Click **Create Index Pattern**</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mystery hunt 2</title>
      <link>/en/start/mysteryhunt/hunt2.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:44:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/start/mysteryhunt/hunt2.html</guid>
      <description>Your customers have complained that Guestbook website is throwing 404 not found errors. Investigate and identify the root cause.
Simulate the scenario Run the command below to simulate the scenario
curl -O https://ant332.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ant332-lab-guide-artifacts/mystery_script_2.sh &amp;amp;&amp;amp; chmod +x mystery_script_2.sh &amp;amp;&amp;amp; ./mystery_script_2.sh $URL3 Hint Remeber we created apache- index? It will have useful information to troubleshoot.
Mystery Solved Open Kibana, Double-click Discover tab. Then choose apache-* index pattern and search for 404 errors. You will see all the logs records that contain 404 errors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Amazon EKS?</title>
      <link>/en/intro/second-content.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:44:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/intro/second-content.html</guid>
      <description>Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) makes it easy to deploy, manage, and scale containerized applications using Kubernetes on AWS.
Amazon EKS runs the Kubernetes management infrastructure for you across multiple AWS availability zones to eliminate a single point of failure. Amazon EKS is certified Kubernetes conformant so you can use existing tooling and plugins from partners and the Kubernetes community. Applications running on any standard Kubernetes environment are fully compatible and can be easily migrated to Amazon EKS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Kibana for apache index</title>
      <link>/en/start/indices/apache.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:44:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/start/indices/apache.html</guid>
      <description>Repeat the previous step again to create an index pattern for apache- index. Click this deep link to open Kibana in your browser and follow the steps below - http://localhost:9200/_plugin/kibana
Click Management tab -&amp;gt; Click Index Patterns -&amp;gt; Click Create Index Pattern -&amp;gt; Type apache-* in input box -&amp;gt; Choose ***@timestamp*** from drop down-&amp;gt; Click **Create Index Pattern**</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mystery hunt 3</title>
      <link>/en/start/mysteryhunt/hunt3.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:44:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/start/mysteryhunt/hunt3.html</guid>
      <description>Your development team has reported that redis performance has degraded over time. They suspect memory fragmentation may be the root cause. They&#39;ve asked for an easy way to get visibility into trend of memory fragmentation over a period of time.
Hint Remember we created the redis- index? Examine the contents of this index and build a visualization in Kibana.
Mystery Solved The redis- index contains all the key redis metrics collected by flunetbit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>